大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかしVIPなエア・フォース
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの どうして？
知らない間に
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
The view along the banks of the Arakawa changes as you draw closer to the sea.
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
Tired-looking secretaries eating lunch.
An absent-minded old man fishing for crayfish.
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
And...
A young couple walking on the riverbank.
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
We're in the middle of our first date.
Chapter 25: "The First Date"
Arakawa
On our first date, Nino-san wished
Warning
Absolutely no swimming!
Arakawa
初デートは ニノさんの希望により
荒川の河口を見に行く事になった
Arakawa
to see the estuary of Arakawa River.
The bridge where we live is approximately twelve kilometers from the estuary.
俺達の住んでいる
橋から河口までは 約12キロ
At the rate we’re going, we should arrive in three hours.
この調子じゃ
３時間もあれば着いてしまう
おっ 珍しい鳥だなあ
It’s unusual to see that bird around here.
Hey, Rec.
なあ リク
Yes, what is it?
はい なんでしょう？
Are the dates you spoke of
デートっていうのは こうやって
ひたすら歩いているものなのか？
about walking like this, with a determined destination?
えっ？ ああ そりゃあ…
Oh, well…
I’d been so relieved that I managed to ask her out on a date that I’d lost focus.
俺としたことが デートに誘えた事に
安心して 気を抜いてしまっていたぜ
What are you talking about, Nino-san?
何を言ってるんですか ニノさん
If you refer to it in terms of a full course meal,
we’ve only arrived at the hors d’oeuvre so far.
今までのは フルコースで
言うところの ほんのオードブル
メインディッシュはこれからです！
From here on will be the main dish,
素晴らしい 愛の旅の始まりですよ！
the beginning of a wonderful journey of love!
おお そうだったのか…
Oh, so that’s what it is.
Despite saying that, what should I do?
とは言ったものの どうする…？
歩かなくては河口にたどり着かない…
However, if we just walk, we won’t accomplish anything.
だが ただ歩くのでは芸がない
Nino-san, allow me to tell you this:
ニノさん 教えて差し上げましょう
The most important thing in love is
恋愛にとって一番大切なもの それは…
距離感です！
distance!
Distance?
距離感？
ええ 俺は昨日一晩で それを学びました
Yes.
Centimeters Till I Reach You
I studied through that last night.
Conflicting paths despite the close proximity!
こんなに近いのにすれ違い…
かと思えば！
Being at a distance but feeling the closeness of your love!
Love Letter from Canada
遠いのに こんなに
近くに感じるあなたの愛！
That is the most important relationship between a man and a woman!
それが男と女の間で
一番大切なものなのです！
... is what
Yuji said.
Oh! In a conflict, going far away, getting close!
おお！ すれ違い 遠ざかり 近づく か！
Right!
そうです！ さすがニノさん！
Impressive, Nino-san!
So, I’m sure we shouldn’t stand this close.
じゃあきっと この立ち位置はいかんな…
そうですね…
初デートにしては近すぎます
That’s right.
We’re too close for a first date.
For now, let’s take at least two steps away.
とりあえず ２歩くらい下がってみますね
Yeah.
それで ニノさん もうちょっと右…
ああ！ 後ろ 川に気をつけて下さい！
And Nino-san, move a little to the right.
Oh, be careful of the river behind you!
心得た
I got it.
うーん… まだちょっと何かが…
There still seems to be something missing.
とっ…！ ちょっとニノさん
これくらい隠れてもらえます？
Hey, Nino-san. Could you hide behind something about this large?
Yeah.
Like this?
こうか？
そうです！ そんな感じで！
Yes! That’s it!
これが！
This feeling is
the distance of a first date!
初デートの距離感！
Probably…
かなあ…
I see.
なるほど… 体得したぞ！
I’ve got it now.
We can do this, Recruit.
行けそうだリクルート… 進むぞ！
Let’s move ahead!
ええっ… ええ！ もちろん！
Yeah, of course!
Oh no, Recruit! There’s nothing to hide behind!
大変だリク！ 隠れる物がないぞ！
Well then…
え ええと… では…
“近いのに遠い”でいきますか！
Shall we try being near while being at a distance?
Crossing paths?
“すれ違い”か！
Crossing paths!
Crossed Signals
すれ違い！
Rec, what’s next?
リク 次は？
What’s the next distance, Recruit?
次の距離感は？ リクルート
Oh, th-that’s right. Next is, uh…
えっと… そうですね 次は… その…
The connected distance between our hearts!
“通じあった心の距離”です！
Th-This is…
こ これが…
The connected distance between our hearts!
The distance of our linked hearts
通じあった心の距離！
Fight on!
ファイッ オー！
ファ ファ…？ リクルート これは…？
F-F…
Recruit, what is this?
It’s a ritual.
儀式ですよ 完成された距離感を祝う
It celebrates the completion of the sense of distance.
おお～ そうか！
Oh, is that so?
We did it, Nino-san.
やりましたね ニノさん！
もう俺達は 距離感マスターですよ！
We’re now masters of distance!
つ 次は…
N-Next?
There’s nothing else.
ありません！
The next–
次の…
There’s absolutely nothing left!
本当に絶対ありません！
Chapter 26: "Laws of Attraction"
I’m so glad.
あー よかった！ いやー これで晴れて
俺達 距離感マスターですね！
Now we’re openly the masters of distance.
やあ～ ほんとよかったですよ 一時は
どうなることかともう… ね～ ほんと…
That’s really great.
For a moment there, I was worried about what would happen.
Hey, Rec.
なあ リク
ドクッ！
In the end, our current situation is no different than before.
結局この状態
はじめと変わっていないんだが…
As I thought, dates are like–
やっぱりデートっていうのはこういう…
やだなあ ニノさん！
Come on, Nino-san!
You can’t possibly think it’s already over.
まさか もう… これで終わりなわけ…
んー ないじゃないですかあ！
Dates are… You know, that…
デートと言ったら あれですよ あれ…！
Yes! Carrying the princess!
そう！ お姫様抱っこです！
Carrying the princess?
おひめさまだっこ？
That’s right.
そうです そう！ これがなきゃ
デートは始まりませんよ！
Without that, a date can’t begin.
それは 具体的にどういう…？
How does that work, specifically?
It’d be faster to try it.
やってみた方が早いでしょう
ニノさん ここに座ってみて下さい
Please sit here, Nino-san.
前です！
The front!
Oh, sorry.
おお すまん！
L-Like this?
こ こうか？
Yes.
そうです！
じゃあニノさん 立ちますよー？
Okay, Nino-san. I’m standing up!
This is a princess carry!
これが！ お姫様抱っこです！
Ow.
痛っ！
あれ？
痛っ！ 痛っ！ 痛っ！ 痛っ！
いてっ！ あいてっ！
Recruit… I hate this “carrying the princess” thing.
リクルート… 私 お姫様抱っこ嫌いだ…
Yeah, my arms have reached their limits, too.
ええ… 俺も腕が限界です…
Somehow, a date spends your physical strength.
何だか デートっていうのは
体力を使うんだなぁ
Yeah.
ええ… ちょっとこの辺で
休んでいきましょうか
Shall we rest here for a while?
We’re almost to the estuary.
もうすぐ 河口ですね
I see.
そうか… どうりで賑やかだな この辺は
No wonder it’s so lively around here.
That’s right.
ですね…
It’s kind of strange…
なんだか不思議だな やっぱり…
As I thought, being with Nino-san at places other than the bridge is…
ニノさんと あの橋以外の所に
いるっていうのは…
Yeah. It feels nice.
そうだ… なんかいい感じだし
せっかくのデートだし
And it’s on a date, too.
I wonder if we can talk about things we usually don’t?
普段できない話をするのはどうだろう…
Yeah. That’s it.
うん そうだよ さっきは何となく
躊躇して 聞けなかった話
The things I couldn’t ask when I was somewhat hesitant earlier.
Hey, Nino-san.
あの… ニノさん？ そういえば…
Come to think of it, the dress that you wore earlier…
さっき着てくれたドレス
I thought it might’ve been difficult to get dressed on your own,
ああいうの １人で着るのって
大変だと思うんですけど…
but you seemed to be quite used to it.
すごく 着慣れてる感じっていうか…
よくああいうの 着てたのかなーとか…
I wondered if you’re used to wearing dresses like that.
I’m pretty curious about your past.
俺 ニノさんの昔の事とか
気になってるんですけど…
Why?
なんで…？
へ？ え いやあ…
Er, well…
あ やっぱり恋人の事ですから
知っておきたいなと…
Naturally, because we’re lovers, I’d like to know.
Rec.
リク… 私は… 今も昔も金星人だ
I have always been a Venusian.
Is that not good enough?
それじゃあダメか？
Come on, Nino-san.
やだな ニノさん… なんで急にそんな顔…
What’s with that expression?
Well, you know…
いえ あの…
えっ？ どうかしましたか？
What’s the matter?
That grass boat…
あの草舟… 私が上流で流したやつだ
It’s the one I set afloat from upstream.
へえー！ すごいじゃないですか！
こんな下流まで…
That’s amazing, isn’t it?
It reached this far downstream.
It couldn’t reach the sea.
海には… 行けなかったな…
The reason for her expression, and Nino-san’s past…
その顔の理由も ニノさんの過去も…
追及したくないと言ったら嘘になる
I’d be lying if I said I didn’t want to pursue those matters,
but as her lover…
けど 恋人として…
Rec!
リク！
There is one thing I should do now.
俺が今やるべき仕事は １つだ
な… リク！ 何してるんだ 危ない…
Rec, what are you doing?
It’s dangerous.
大丈夫です！
It’s okay.
It’s okay, Nino-san.
大丈夫ですよ ニノさん！
That boat can still float on–
あの舟 まだまだ進めますっ
ぶっ…！ うっ…
Rec! You idiot.
リク！ バカ！ 早く上がれ！
ここは流れが…
Get up here, quickly!
The currents here are–
Hey! Look, Nino-san!
ほら！ ニノさん見て！
That splash got the boat moving again!
今のしぶきで 舟が進みましたよ！
It moved with such a small amount of stimulation.
こんな些細なきっかけで動くんです
あいつ 太平洋まで行けますよ
It could go all the way to the Pacific Ocean.
よし！ じゃあ 俺達も行きましょうか
All right.
Shall we go too?
Rec.
リク…
If you don’t mind someone who has always been and will always be an Earthling,
今も昔もこれからも地球人の
俺とでよかったら… 一緒に
let’s go together.
Yeah.
Huh? Nino-san, your face is red.
あれ？ ニノさん？
顔赤いですが 具合でも？
Are you not feeling well?
Are you hurting somewhere?
どこか 痛かったりしないですか？
No.
いや？ 夕日だろ？
It’s probably the sunset.
For example,
D
I
F
E
R
N
T
PLANET
例えば 星が違っても
男女の違いがあっても
even if we’re from different planets
DIFFERENT SEX
and are of different genders…
Whether it’s a relationship with the opposite sex or another planet,
どちらの“いせいかんこうりゅう”も
平仮名で書けば 変わらない
in simpler terms, they mean the same.
Chapter 27: "Stella"
Company,
全員！
fall in!
整列！
Michael’s stance!
ミカエルの構え！
サキエルの構え！
Sachiel’s stance!
Secret technique:
奥義 ユダの裏切り！
Betrayal of Judah!
よし！ 皆動きがよくなってきたな
All right.
You’ve all improved.
Who’s that?!
誰だ！ 号令前に動くことは許さ…
Moving before the command is unforgi–
I wanted to meet Sister!
I wanted to meet sister!
Stella?
ステラか？
Hi!
ハイ！
S-Someone he knows?
し 知り合いか？
Oh, she’s cute.
ええ～っ 可愛い子だね！
She sure is.
ほんとだぁ！
あ… ミ ミナサン コンニチハ…
H-Hello, everyone.
She can speak Japanese.
日本語話せるんだあ！
すごい すごーい！
That’s great!
Sister, who’s that girl?
シスター その子は？
I’ve no choice. Let me introduce her.
仕方ない 紹介しよう
This girl is Stella,
彼女はステラ 私がイギリスの孤児院で
面倒を見ていた娘の１人だ
a girl I took care of at an orphanage in England.
England?
イギリス…！
I see. It had crossed my mind that Sister isn’t Japanese.
そうか シスターは日本人じゃないとは
思っていたけど…
Good grief.
まったく… 追い返すわけにもいかんな…
I can’t send you away now.
I’m going to call my homeland. Can someone watch her?
本国に電話してくる
誰か 構ってやっていてくれ
Yes! We’ll do it!
はいはーい！ 僕達が！
Oh, we can’t!
あっ ダメだ！ 今日は研究所の奴らが…
The guys from the research place are coming.
Oh yeah, those guys.
そうだった… あいつらが…！
I’m going fishing after this,
私も今から
魚を捕らんといかんからなあ…
しかし…
but we can’t just leave her alone.
いきなり１人にするわけにも
いかないし… 困ったなあ…
How troubling.
Hm, really troubling.
うーん 困った… ああー 困ったなあ！
Oh, how troubling.
来る…！ お守りをしろと
今すぐにも言いだしそうな空気だ！
It’s coming…
There’s a pressure to speak up now,
even though I know it’s babysitting…
I’d rather avoid anything troublesome,
面倒なのはごめんだし
正直子供は苦手なんだ…
and truthfully, I’m bad with kids.
I feel sorry for Nino-san and the rest,
ニノさん達には悪いけど この橋の下には
暇人なんてわんさかいるし
but there are so many people with free time under this bridge.
俺は今のうちに 退散しとこう！
I should take this chance to break away now.
ゴクッ…
What’s with that picture like at the end of the episode?
何 その最終回みたいな絵…？
Rec-san!
リクさん…！
My lover’s so kind.
私の恋人は優しいな
I think I should learn from their speedy decision.
あいつらの決断力の速さは
見習うべきものだと思いました
かわさきがっぱ♪
Chapter 28: "Let's Play Together"
め めんどくさい…
What a hassle.
I don’t even know what to talk about.
何話したらいいかも分かんないし…
とりあえず さりげなく
１人遊びさせる方向に…
For now, I should nonchalantly lead her to play on her own…
うふふ…
Hm? What is it?
何？ どうしたの？
Oh, sorry!
あ！ ごめんなさい！ お兄ちゃんが
できたみたいで 嬉しくって…
This feels like I have a big brother, so I’m really happy.
あ… 君 兄弟は？
Do you have any siblings?
Come to think of it, this girl grew up in an orphanage.
そういえばこの子は 孤児院育ち…
天涯孤独なんじゃないか…！
She doesn’t have any relatives, does she?
えへっ
Even though I only have my father,
俺も父親しかいなかったけど
この子には どっちもいなかったんだ…
this girl doesn’t have either parent.
What’s wrong?
どうしたの？
I see.
そうか… 今日１日の偽物だけど
Even though it’s not real,
it’ll be nice to be her brother, just for today.
お兄さんになってあげるのも
いいかもしれないな
Okay, Stella. Shall we play together?
よし ステラ 一緒に遊ぼうか！
Really?
ほんとー？
うん！ 何がしたい？ なんでもいいよ！
What would you like to do?
Anything’s fine.
うわぁ… わお！
That made her so happy.
こんなに喜ぶなんて…
イギリスでシスターとも別れて
１人で生きていたんだろうか…
Could she have been living alone since she got separated from Sister in England?
Anything at all?
なんでも？
Of course.
もちろん！
Um, um…
えーっとね えーっとね
She must have been really lonely.
寂しかったんだろうな…
I’ve never played with a girl,
女の子の遊びなんてした事ないけど
なんでもしてあげよう！
but I’ll join her in anything.
Uh, well, I…
あ あのね ステラね
…would like to…
お兄ちゃんと…
…compete in a one-on-one battle.
タイマン… はりたいなぁ！
Taimai?
タイ… マイ…？
No, I’m not talking about rice.
ううん お米じゃなくて メンツをかけた
ルール無用の残虐ファイッ だよ！
It’s a brutal fight where you bet your honor and rules are futile!
I forgot that she was brought up by Sister!
シスターに育てられてた事を
忘れてました！
Chapter 29: "Battle for Big Bro"
タイマンしたいって… 言葉の意味
分かんないで言ってんだろうなぁ…
A one-on-one battle…
She must have said it without knowing what it means.
んん？ なんだステラ 早速タイマンか？
What is it, Stella?
Getting down to battle already?
あ… イエス！
Yes!
Sister, you shouldn’t teach a girl games like that.
シスター ダメですよ！
女の子にこんな遊び教えちゃ！
There are girls’ games that frail girls can play.
か弱い女の子には 女の子の
遊びがあるんですからね！
Frail?
か弱い？ なんだリク 見てなかったのか？
Why, Rec, didn’t you see it?
See what?
何をです？
ステラの必殺技 “特攻”だよ
Stella’s special move.
It’s the “Suicidal.”
She grabbed my neck even though I had a gun.
銃を構えた私の首を押さえる事が
できるのなんて ステラくらいだぞ
Only Stella could do that.
That’s just a hug, isn’t it?
あんなの ただのハグじゃないですか
And you allowed it because Stella’s so adorable, right?
そんなのシスターにとって
ステラが可愛いからでしょ！
Did I?
そうなのか？ 私はいつでも
全力で迎え撃つ気でいるんだが…
I’ve always retaliated with all my might, though.
あっははは！ そうですよ！
That is it.
Come, Stella.
さあ ステラ タイマンしよう！ 行くよー！
Let’s battle.
Here I go.
To avoid hurting her, I should lose quickly.
怪我させないように
早々に負けてあげなきゃな…
Ah, you dodged it…
わー よけられちゃったぁ
Oh, this is grea—
おー こりゃすご…
ドクッ ドクッ ドクッ…
べぐっ べぐっ… ぎゃっ ぎゃっ…
Stella!
ステラ！
You can only use three-move combos on normal folk.
一般人には ３コンボまでだぞ！
はあっ！ ミステーイク！
Mistake!
うぎゃあっ…
えへ…
Rec, what are you doing?
リク 何をしているんだ？
Uh, what, you say…
いや 何っていうか… 俺が聞きたい！
I’d like to know, too! What just happened?!
何が起きたの 今！
ステラ お兄ちゃんと
タイマンごっこしてたの！
I played battle with my big brother.
Oh.
パタッ
やるなリク わざと負けてやったのか？
Well done, Rec. You lost to her on purpose.
え！ わざと？ そうなの？ 俺
On purpose?
Was that what I did?
Somehow, it felt like I was flung in the air and beaten up,
なんか宙に浮かされて
ボコられたような気がしたけど…
but, certainly, I didn’t get serious with her.
確かに全然 本気なんて
出してなかったもんなあ…
I had lots of fun!
ステラとっても楽しかったよ！
Stella.
ステラ…
I’m glad.
よかった…
Um… How do I say this…
あの なんて言うか… ここにいる間は
俺を兄貴だと思っていいからね
While you’re here, you can think of me as a big brother.
Rec-san!
リクさん… センキューです！
Thank you!
うふっ…
I’ve always disliked kids,
今まで子供を毛嫌いしてたけど…
素直な子なら 結構…
but obedient kids are quite…
You have to win the battle to be the “Big Bro.”
兄貴面できるなぁ
タイマンで勝った方じゃ
From now on, you’ll just be a grunt.
今日からわりゃぁ わしの舎弟じゃい
The fish is grilled. Want to eat?
魚が焼けたぞー 食うかー？
Yes!
はあーい！
A fairy with a Hiroshima dialect?
広島弁の妖精さん…？ 幻聴かなぁ…？
Could it be auditory hallucination?
Chapter 30: "Maria"
When kids seem to be playing along nicely together,
子供達が仲良く
遊んでいる様子というのは
it is, indeed, just what plays in your mind.
実に 心洗われる光景であるが…
Rec-san!
リクさーん！
Hello.
こんにちは！ いい天気だね！
The weather’s great, isn’t it?
Oh… Yeah.
Huh? What’s this?
あれ？ なんだ やっぱり
いい子なんじゃないか？
She must be a nice girl after all.
A kid like her couldn’t have called me a grunt.
こんな子が 舎弟とか言うわけないや…
Hi there, Stella. Today–
こんにちは ステラ 今日も…
Hey!
オラァァァ！
How dare you carelessly address her so casually, Rec?!
何軽々しく呼び捨てしとんじゃあ リク！
At least use -san when addressing the Boss!
ボスには最低でも “さん”付け
じゃろうが アホンダラァ！
D-Don’t tell me you guys have become Stella’s grunts.
な！ まさかお前ら ステラの舎弟に…
Rec.
リク…
I must have both of your big brothers teach you how to speak.
兄さんら２人に ようけ口のきき方
教えてもらうんじゃのう…
Come on, let’s go, both of you!
さあ行くわよ ２人とも！
Yes, Boss!
イエス！ ボス！
わはっ わはは… あはは…
おっ 俺が一番下かあーっ！
I’m at the lowest level?!
うっ… あ… くっ… なぜだ…
なぜどんどん 敵が増えていくんだぁ…
Why?
Why do my enemies keep increasing in number?
Hey, Rec.
おお リク ここにいたのか
Here you are.
あっ… シスター
Sister…
Sorry, but would you come with me on an errand?
すまんが ちょっと
おつかいに付き合ってくれんか？
重い物を運ぶ事になるかもしれんのだ
You may have to carry some heavy stuff, though.
With this wagon?
このワゴンでですか？ いいですけど…
Yeah, sure.
シスターに運べない物を
俺が運べるのか？
Can I lift something that Sister can’t?
Thanks.
ありがたい
いったい 何のおつかいですか？
What are we going for, exactly?
Ingredients for a cake.
ケーキの材料だ ステラの
歓迎パーティを 開いてやろうと思ってな
I thought we’d have a welcoming party for Stella.
Oh, I should work hard, then…
わあ それは頑張らなくちゃね
Is something wrong?
どうかしたか？
No, nothing at all.
いいえ… 何でもないです
A cake, eh?
ケーキって？ それじゃあ
橋の外に買い出しですか？
So, are we going out to buy one?
No, we’re going over there.
いや あそこだ
Over there?
あそこって？ あ…
S-Sister, these sounds…
シ シスター？ なんか鳴き声が…
動物の鳴き声が聞こえるんですが！
I hear the sounds of animals.
Yeah, that’s right.
ああ そうだろう 何せ 牧場だからな
At any rate, that’s the farm.
All the dairy products for the riverbed are from here.
河川敷の乳製品などは
全てここで賄われていてだな…
What’s wrong, Rec?
どうした？ リク
国は何をしているんですか！
What is the government doing about this?!
Well, that doesn’t matter, does it?
まあいいじゃないか
ここの牛乳はおいしいぞ
The milk here is delicious.
はっ はは… そして どうせここも
変な人が管理しているんでしょ？
And naturally, it’s run by someone weird, right?
I’ve had enough of meeting new people!
もう嫌だ！ 新しい出会いは…
What are you saying?
何を言う！ ここの人はとても…
The person here is truly–
Oh my, Sister?
あら シスター！
Hello there. How are you today?
こんにちは お元気かしら？
Maria.
マリア…
Maria-san?
マリアさん？
Wow.
わ… 綺麗で優しそうな人だ…
まさにマリアって名前がぴったり…
She’s beautiful and looks like a nice person.
The name Maria seems so apt for her.
Guess that kappa does give some good names sometimes.
河童もたまには
マシなネーミングするんだな…
ああ こんにちは！ 俺…
Oh, hello. I’m–
Oh, it’s okay.
ああ いいの！ いいのよ しゃべらないで
It’s fine. You don’t have to speak.
It’d be a waste of Earth’s valuable oxygen.
地球上の貴重な酸素が もったいないから
If an existence like yours is going to continue,
あなたみたいのが存在し続けたいのなら
二酸化炭素を吸って 酸素を生み出す
練習でもしたらどうかしら？
how about you practice breathing in carbon dioxide and creating oxygen instead?
Chapter 31: "Blood Service"
Don’t worry about it, Rec.
Why is it, Sister,
that I somehow feel the basis of my existence has just been rejected?
あの日夕暮れ
Like I’ve been told to drop dead?
Hey!
Calm down, Rec.
Even though she said you’re lower than grass,
that is just an expression of her love.
Lower than grass?!
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
I’m sorry, Rec-kun.
Actually, I heard about you yesterday.
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
You’re so cute that I can’t help but tease you.
You told me to die!
That was beyond the definition of teasing!
I seriously lost the strength to live.
You told me to die!
もう行かなくちゃ
Your reactions are great.
この空泣き出す前に
I like that.
I’m Maria. Pleased to meet you.
サカサマになって
Sister!
I really don’t like this person…
君の事探して
The people here are foulmouthed,
but her wicked tongue seems somewhat different.
いつまでも僕らは
たどり着けないまま
Rec, aren’t you glad that she likes you?
橋の下に立って
So, Maria, I’ve come to get milk and eggs today.
流れる渦に在って
いつまでも僕らは
Sure, I have some.
Wh-Why did he scowl at me?
Sca ry...
その答え探して
Sure, it’s wrong to speak badly of others,
but even Sister would be annoyed if he were blasted by that wicked mouth.
Sister,
would you mind not casting a shadow on the ground?
The sun does not have the leisure to shine on you.
Sorry.
She’s unharmed?!
大丈夫か？ リク
はがっ…！ な なんですか シスター
Suffocating.
Sorry.
Annoying.
今俺 なんか存在を
根底から否定されたような…
Sorry.
Cross-dresser.
I’m sorry.
死ねっつわれた
気がするんですけど… あのっ！
Pervert.
Forgive me.
Lolicon.
Sorry.
Good-for-nothing.
落ち着け リク
I apologize.
Old hag.
確かにお前は“草以下”と言われたが
それは彼女の愛情表現だ
Sorry.
Self-centered.
I’ll reflect on it.
Voodoo.
Sorry.
A-Amazing!
草以下！
うっふふふ… ごめんね リクくん
Even though she said all that,
his expression remained unchanged.
You really have no reactions at all, Sister.
本当はもうあなたの事は
聞いていたんだけど
Serves you right!
あたしつい可愛い人には
意地悪を言っちゃうのよね…
Stuff like that won’t work on Sister!
意地悪とか そういう次元の
発言じゃなかったですよ！
You’re such a bore.
俺 マジで生きる力を失うかと…
Sorry.
ふふふ… あなた 反応がとっても
いいのね… あたし気に入っちゃった…
マリアよ よろしくね
よっ… あ あ あ… シスター！
俺本気で嫌です この人…
Sister!
Oh my!
It sounded like an elephant fell.
ここの人達 口悪いけど
この人の毒舌は 何か質が違う…
Chapter 32: "Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge"
リク よかったじゃないか 気に入られて
それでマリア 今日は卵と牛乳を
もらいに来たんだが…
We'll try a joke!
ええ あるわよ
な なんで俺が
睨まれなきゃいけないんだ？
Iron Mask, falling back!
確かに悪口はいけないけど
Copycat
Sorry
Try again
いくらシスターだって あの毒舌を
くらったら ムカつくくらいするはず！
あ シスター！ なるべく地面に
影を作らないで下さる？
Rec, eat this cookie!
太陽もあなたを照らしているほど
暇じゃないから…
I don’t really want it.
Are you sayin’ the cookie I made is inedible?
ひいっ！
すまん
I’ll eat it, I’ll eat it, okay?
どっ…！ 無傷！
Next time: 5 Bridge.
Hey, you really ate it.
What? What’s that remote control in your hand?!
暑苦しい
Illustration: Ken Yagami
すまん
うざい
女装癖
すまない
-変態
-すまん
-ロリコン
でくのぼう
申し訳ない
おかちめんこ
ごめん
おてもやん
謝意を表する
ウド
ソーリー
す すげえ！あれだけの事を言われても
顔色一つ変えないなんて…
ほんとにシスターは無反応ね…
ざまーみろ！ シスターにそんなのは
効かないんだよ！ ふははは…！
ふ… つまんない人…
すま…
シスターッ！
あはっ あらまあ！
象が倒れたような音がしました
リク！ ほれクッキーじゃ
いや 別にいらないけど…
わしのこねたクッキーが
食えんて言うのか？
あ… 食べるよぉ！
食べればいいんだろ！ はむっ…
次回 「５ BRIDGE」
へへっ わらぁ 確かに食べたな
えっ 何？ その手に持ったリモコン！